const e="civiledu",o=200,a=99,i=[{id:97,question:"The channel through which political parties make their program known to the people is ..............",option:{a:"canvassing",b:"campaigning",c:"convincing",d:"coronation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:98,question:"What arm of the criminal justice system is prison?",option:{a:"first",b:"second",c:"third",d:"none"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:99,question:"................ is the apex body saddled by law to fight corruption and other related offences",option:{a:"IRS",b:"ICPC",c:"EFCC",d:"NPF"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:100,question:"The responsibility of protecting past and present high ranking government officials falls on ...............",option:{a:"police",b:"army",c:"civil defense corps",d:"SSS"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:101,question:"............ is obtained from the Nigerian immigration services as a requirement to travel out of the country",option:{a:"ticket",b:"yellow card",c:"passport",d:"national ID card"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:102,question:"There are ............. local government in Nigeria",option:{a:"700",b:"714",c:"744",d:"774"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:103,question:"Local government is the ............... tier of government",option:{a:"1st",b:"2nd",c:"3rd",d:"4th"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:104,question:"Television and radio are example  of ......... media",option:{a:"print",b:"electronic",c:"advertising",d:"mass"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:105,question:"Newspapers and magazine and example of ..... media",option:{a:"print",b:"electronic",c:"advertising",d:"mass"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:106,question:"One of the listed criteria qualifies one for election .......",option:{a:"certificate",b:"beauty",c:"height",d:"citizenship"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:107,question:"The following are duties to be performed by the citizens of a country EXCEPT",option:{a:"Destroying government properties",b:"obey law and order",c:"payment of tax",d:"show loyalty"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:108,question:"The form of government in which the electorate exercise their governing power directly through their elected 	representation is called ........",option:{a:"supremacy",b:"democracy",c:"autocracy",d:"charismatic"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:109,question:"Punishment for law breaking include the following except ..........",option:{a:"freedom of movement",b:"detention",c:"sanctions",d:"political instability"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:110,question:"The act of counting the numbers of people living in a country in order to determine the total numbers of 	people in a state is known as .......",option:{a:"election",b:"national population census",c:"voting",d:"rights"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:111,question:"The last population census in Nigeria was conducted in ...........",option:{a:"2003",b:"2006",c:"2007",d:"2005"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:112,question:"The 219 chibok girls were ................ while ..............",option:{a:"abducted, praying in the mosque",b:"kidnaped, praying in the church",c:"abducted, wondering along the street of chibok town",d:"kidnaped, preparing to write their WAEC examination"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:113,question:"The following are types of drugs except",option:{a:"cannabis",b:"depressants",c:"benzodiazepine pines",d:"steroids"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:114,question:"Cocaine, morphine and heroin are example of",option:{a:"tobacco",b:"steroids",c:"narcotics",d:"inhalants"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:115,question:"......... refer to a group of drugs that are inhaled in the form of a gas or solvent",option:{a:"hallucinogens",b:"stimulants",c:"inhalants",d:"gasoline"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:116,question:"Cannabis is also called .........",option:{a:"barbiturates",b:"cassava",c:"marijuana",d:"caffeine"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:117,question:"Which of the following is the most common forms of drug abuse",option:{a:"drug trafficking",b:"self medication",c:"drug combination",d:"frequent use"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:118,question:"The following factors are responsible for drug abuse except",option:{a:"family upbringing",b:"high stress level",c:"poverty",d:"foster parenthood"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:119,question:"........ is the type of parenthood where a different couple raise a particular child that is not their own",option:{a:"helicopter parent",b:"foster parenthood",c:"slow parenting",d:"different parenthood"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:120,question:"One of the following is a cause of single parents in Nigeria",option:{a:"slow parenting",b:"social group",c:"nature of work",d:"divorce"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:121,question:".......... strengthens the sensitive mental and emotional bond between the parent and children",option:{a:"narcissistic parenting",b:"attachment parenting",c:"positive parenting",d:"teenage parenting"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:122,question:"........... is the verdict that results when a law court declares a defendant guilty of a crime",option:{a:"immunity clause",b:"conviction",c:"customary clause",d:"traditions"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:123,question:"The clause which exempts the president from being prosecuted while still in office is called",option:{a:"military clause",b:"special clause",c:"conviction clause",d:"immunity clause"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:124,question:"All the following can limit the right of a citizen except",option:{a:"war",b:"state of emergency",c:"universality",d:"military rule"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:125,question:"The following are causes of emergency rule except",option:{a:"crisis",b:"blood lettings",c:"stage peaceful protest",d:"sabotage / terrorism"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:126,question:"The World AIDs Day is usually ..........................",option:{a:"June 12th every year",b:"May second every year",c:"October 1st every year",d:"December 1st every year"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:127,question:"One of the following is not human right group",option:{a:"Constitutional Right Project (CRP)",b:"National Association of Democratic Lawyers (NADL)",c:"Nigeria Bar Association (NBA)",d:"Civil Liberties Organization (CLO)"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:128,question:"One of the following is not a pressure group",option:{a:"National Association of Nigeria Student (NANS)",b:"Nigeria Labour Congress (NLC)",c:"Academic Staff Union of Universities (ASUU)",d:"Committee for Defense of Human Right (CDHR)"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:129,question:"One of the following is not a political party",option:{a:"PDP",b:"APGA",c:"ANPC",d:"CPC"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:130,question:"One of the following is a social group",option:{a:"dangote group of companies",b:"rotary club",c:"Millan group",d:"human right Africa"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:131,question:"The organization with the motives and goals of helping people is called",option:{a:"social group",b:"charity group",c:"pressure group",d:"human right group"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:132,question:"The following are the reasons why people do not participate in polities except",option:{a:"illiteracy",b:"lack of justice",c:"multi-party system",d:"religion"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:133,question:"............... is the prejudicial treatment of fellow human being",option:{a:"god fatherism",b:"independence",c:"justice",d:"discrimination"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:134,question:"Laws are interpreted by the",option:{a:"Judiciary",b:"President",c:"Legislature",d:"Executive"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:135,question:"The president belongs to ............... arm of the government",option:{a:"Executive",b:"Judiciary",c:"Military",d:"Legislature"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:136,question:"The process whereby an individual choose to favour a person who come from his family or tribe over other people or tribes is known as",option:{a:"stereotype",b:"ethnicity",c:"nepotism",d:"favouritism"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:137,question:"When a group of people believe in and keep to certain norms, values and ways of life of their community since its creation, we call this .................",option:{a:"religion",b:"stereotypes",c:"traditions",d:"custom"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:138,question:"Traffic lights are also known and referred to as",option:{a:"three directives light",b:"spotlight",c:"flow traffic directive",d:"informative sign"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:139,question:"One of the following is not a federal road agencies",option:{a:"DTO",b:"FRSC",c:"TRACE",d:"VIO"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:140,question:"One of the following is a regulatory prohibitory sign",option:{a:"stop police",b:"speed limit",c:"t junction",d:"ferry"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:141,question:"The traffic light has how many colours",option:{a:"3",b:"4",c:"5",d:"2"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:142,question:"From the basic road traffic regulation pedestrians should not attempt to cross the road when the light are ............. and ...............",option:{a:"green and yellow",b:"green and red",c:"yellow and red",d:"red and yellow"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:143,question:"Motorcyclists must always protect their heads with safety ............. which must be properly fastened",option:{a:"seat belt",b:"head guild",c:"helmets",d:"cap cycles"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:144,question:"Pedestrians should always cross road using",option:{a:"stop hold",b:"parked vehicles",c:"zebra crossing",d:"bridge"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:145,question:"The former NAFDAC DG Prof Dora Akunyili died on",option:{a:"June 9. 2014",b:"June 17, 2014",c:"June 7, 2014",d:"May 27, 2014"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"wassce",examyear:"2012"},{id:146,question:"Political values are acquired in any given society through",option:{a:"Political re-orientation",b:"Political campaign",c:"Political socialization",d:"Political indoctrination"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:147,question:"To ensure the rights and freedom of citizens; the power of the arms of government must be",option:{a:"fused",b:"incorporated",c:"separated",d:"rotated"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:148,question:"The right of citizens to participate in the affairs of government of their country is called",option:{a:"economic right",b:"civil right",c:"political right",d:"social right"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:149,question:"The commission charged with the conduct of federal 	elections in Nigeria between 2014 and 2015 is..........",option:{a:"Nec",b:"fedeco",c:"Inec",d:"Necon"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:150,question:"The colour of the Nigeria flag is ..............., anytime it 	is half masked it means that the nation is ...............",option:{a:"green white green - rejoicing",b:"white green white - mourning",c:"green white green - mourning",d:"green white blue - voting"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:151,question:"Which of the following is used in gauging public opinion",option:{a:"Constitution",b:"Educational Institution",c:"Mass media",d:"Electoral college"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:152,question:"In Nigeria, The agency mainly responsible for the maintenance of internal peace and security is the",option:{a:"Army",b:"Navy",c:"Civil  defense corps",d:"Police"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:153,question:"The National Assembly in Nigeria is primarily responsible for",option:{a:"executing laws",b:"Interpreting laws",c:"ratifying appointment",d:"making laws"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:154,question:"The major factor militating against efficient operation 	of electoral commission in Nigeria is .......................",option:{a:"Inadequate public support",b:"Population size",c:"Inadequate skilled manpower",d:"excessive political interference"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:155,question:"When Ebola disease is very rampant ............. count 	their loses while ......... smile to the bank",option:{a:"fish sellers, bush meat sellers",b:"bush meat sellers, fish sellers",c:"bread sellers, fish sellers",d:"students, teachers"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:156,question:"Workers in the Public Corporations are known as",option:{a:"Civil servants",b:"Private employees",c:"Public servants",d:"Professional employees"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:157,question:"Membership of a society is",option:{a:"conventional",b:"Mandatory",c:"Voluntary",d:"Constitutional"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:158,question:"The necessary attributes of a state are",option:{a:"resources, population, sovereignty and government",b:"sovereignty, police, army and immigration",c:"definite territory, population, sovereignty and government",d:"Police, Army, sovereignty and custom"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:159,question:"Citizenship is acquired by an alien through",option:{a:"registration",b:"birth",c:"Conferment",d:"Naturalization"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:160,question:"The office responsible for announcing the result of an election is known as",option:{a:"ballot officer",b:"presiding officer",c:"Returning officer",d:"Electoral officer"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:161,question:"Law made by military governments are called",option:{a:"decrees",b:"Bye-laws",c:"Edicts",d:"acts"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:162,question:"The ultimate aim of political parties is to",option:{a:"implement people oriented programmes",b:"acquire and exercise power",c:"increase the political awareness of the electorate",d:"formulate and implement policies"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:163,question:"The main objective of pressure groups is to",option:{a:"promote the interest of political parties",b:"influence legislation for the benefit of their member",c:"protect the interest of the country against foreigners",d:"serve as opposition to the government"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:164,question:"Public servants in Nigeria belong to the ............. arm of government",option:{a:"military",b:"executive",c:"legislature",d:"judiciary"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:165,question:"One of the main duties of the local government service commission is to",option:{a:"supervise and manage the personnel of local government",b:"conduct election into local council",c:"create an enabling working environment for council workers",d:"handle request for the creation of more local government"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:166,question:"The option A4 model was used in the conduct of the",option:{a:"2007 election",b:"1983 election",c:"1993 election",d:"1999 election"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:167,question:"The following is the function of a responsible parenthood",option:{a:"care and love",b:"gambling",c:"Drug addition",d:"fighting"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:168,question:"Custom refers to .............",option:{a:"tradition or social value or patterns",b:"image of a country",c:"sharing similar or common ethnic background",d:"A state of feeling of oneness among the people"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:169,question:"The term V. I. O. mean",option:{a:"Vehicle inspection officer",b:"vehicle implementation officer",c:"vehicle induce operation",d:"vehicle induction officer"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:170,question:"Which of these countries operate a unitary system of 	government",option:{a:"Nigeria",b:"U. S. A",c:"Ghana",d:"Britain"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:171,question:"Which of the following are not fundamental human right",option:{a:"right to life",b:"right to gainful employment",c:"right to vote and be voted for",d:"right to overthrow a government"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:172,question:"A constitution that is very easy to amend is called a ...... constitution",option:{a:"rigid",b:"flexible",c:"an easy",d:"simple"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:173,question:"In a democratic government, political sovereignty is vested in the",option:{a:"legislature",b:"elite",c:"executive",d:"electorate"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:174,question:"One judicial function performed by the executive is",option:{a:"granting of amnesty",b:"implementing judicial order",c:"ensuring obedience to the law",d:"appointing judges"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:175,question:"A governmental system in which constitutional supremacy resides in the centre is",option:{a:"federal",b:"confederal",c:"unitary",d:"parliamentary"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:176,question:"The private ownership of the means of production is a feature of",option:{a:"capitalism",b:"Socialism",c:"Communalism",d:"Communism"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:177,question:"A government is said to be legitimate if it",option:{a:"has the people’s mandate to rule",b:"is not oppressive",c:"provide social services for the people",d:"accepts people’s criticism"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:178,question:"All type of government perform all the following functions except",option:{a:"providing welfare and developmental facilities",b:"maintaining law and order",c:"encouraging the struggle for power",d:"encouraging trade with other state"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:179,question:"A coup d’etat is regarded as",option:{a:"A source of political legitimacy",b:"A manipulation of the constitution",c:"A constitutional way of changing the government",d:"an unconstitutional way of changing the government"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:180,question:"Which of the following is an advantage of local government",option:{a:"Agents for money based politics",b:"electoral commissions",c:"training grounds for political leaders",d:"agents of pressure group"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:181,question:"Public Corporations are financed",option:{a:"by tax payers",b:"with private funds",c:"with entrepreneurial funds",d:"by political parties"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:182,question:"A manifesto refers to",option:{a:"the register of party members",b:"rejected ballot papers",c:"valid ballot papers",d:"Document containing the aims and programmes of   a political party"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:183,question:"Which of the following is not a duty of a citizen",option:{a:"obedience to the law",b:"payment of taxes",c:"service to the Nation",d:"giving alms to the poor"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:184,question:"The police perform all the following function except",option:{a:"public execution of law breaker",b:"controlling and directing traffic",c:"protection of life and property",d:"enforcement of law and orders"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:185,question:"An agreed set of rules prescribing the governance of a country can be called the",option:{a:"constitution",b:"charter",c:"manifesto",d:"programme"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:186,question:"The lack of interest in politics by many citizens in a country is called",option:{a:"civic agitation",b:"mass apathy",c:"mass protest",d:"political unrest"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:187,question:"The following are ways to prevent drug addiction except",option:{a:"civic education",b:"law enforcement and regulation",c:"mass media effort",d:"voting at election"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:188,question:"The following are examples of pressure group except",option:{a:"N. U. R. T",b:"NBA",c:"NLC",d:"PDP"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:189,question:"The following are Road Traffic signs except",option:{a:"Regulatory sign",b:"Informative sign",c:"Warning sign",d:"Philosophy sign"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:190,question:"The function of Federal Road Safety Corp (FRSC) is",option:{a:"Enforcing the traffic regulation on road",b:"making law",c:"executing law",d:"Interpreting law"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:191,question:"The function of vehicle inspection officer (VIO) is",option:{a:"ensuring the road wordiness of vehicle on the road",b:"protection of life and property",c:"collection of tax",d:"counting of votes cast at election"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:192,question:"Colonization of Africa was mainly motivated by",option:{a:"security consideration",b:"economic reasons",c:"religious reasons",d:"cultural factor"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:193,question:"Which of these is a type of parenthood",option:{a:"single parenthood",b:"ethnic parenthood",c:"village parenthood",d:"clan parenthood"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:194,question:"Decrees are laws made by ............",option:{a:"Democratic government",b:"The prime minister",c:"The military",d:"Parliaments"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"},{id:195,question:"Austerity measure was first introduced in Nigeria by ..........",option:{a:"President Babangida",b:"Olusegun Obasanjo",c:"President Sehu Shagari",d:"President Goodluck Jonathan"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"neco",examyear:"2012"}],t={subject:e,status:200,total:99,data:i};export{i as data,t as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
